Do you fit his profile?
The Ungodly is a horror, thriller film directed by Thomas Dunn.
When struggling filmmaker inadvertently records a notorious serial killer in the middle of a murderous act, he
decides to use the footage to blackmail the madman into being the subject of a disturbing new documentary.
Mickey Gravatski, played by Wes Bentley.
Emma Lemac, played by Beth Grant.
Megan, played by Joanne Baron.
Jennifer, played by Marina Gatell.
Officer Murphy, played by Kenny Johnson.
Gino, played by Albert López-Murtra.
Halle Lynn Bailey ( HAL-ee; born March 27, 2000), also known mononymously
as Halle, is an American singer-songwriter and actress.
She first became known as a member of the musical duo
Chloe x Halle with her sister Chloe Bailey.
They have released the albums The Kids Are Alright (2018) and Ungodly Hour
(2020), and have together earned five Grammy Award nominations.
In 2023, Bailey released her debut solo single "Angel", which was
nominated for the Grammy Award for Best R&B Song.
On October 24, 2025, she released her debut solo studio album Love?...
or Something Like It.
As an actress, Bailey starred in the television sitcom Grown-ish (2018–2022).
In 2023, she had her first lead role as Ariel in Disney's musical fantasy film The Little
Mermaid and had a supporting role in the musical film The Color Purple.
The film explores themes of rape, psychopath, blackmail, murder, serial killer.
The tone is dark and intense.